You've all been fooled by him
Conscience
What conscience does he have
Do you know about this batch of frogs
How much it can make
10 million
10 million guys
Who earned this 10 million for him
It was us
We worked from dawn to dusk
Worked to death for him
And the result
He bought a tri-fold phone for himself
Tens of thousands for one
Bought big gold bracelets
for his parents
Over 20000 each
Bought designer bags for his wife
40 or 50 thousand each
Jason is right
Why does he get all the meat
While we don't even get the scraps
Exactly
Boss Daniel across the street
He has a real conscience
Knowing I got the skills
He pays me 30000 a month
And look at us
Only making 8000 a month
Not even enough for him to buy a bag
My god
Jason
You're gonna be rich
You bet
I got the skills
You guys can't compare
But
You guys can unite
And demand a raise
This batch of frogs is due next month
A 10 million order
It's the critical period right now
If you all resign together
Can he manage it alone
Three greenhouses and 50000 frogs
Yeah
He definitely can't handle it alone
By then he'll have to
Beg us on his knees to come back
Exactly go find him
No raise then we all resign
In order to deliver on time
He will definitely give in
By then you can name
Whatever price you want
How much you want a month
It's all up to you
Let's go find the boss
No raise
Then we all resign
Right
He just got a huge order
He's definitely more anxious than us
Let's go right now